the next interesting extension will be on every team so first i ask to a gpt what actually i
need i want to have a to the list so first it ask for five these questions what kind of
information would you like to display whatever reminders are you envisioning and how often
should this remind us appear they want to include an integration for now i don't want to
include like a ps and then possible video or a bold data and what um so i want to say
in typical of the slim and here we have a plan and how have them architecture and design
so first i want to have like a simple setup i can use this on in list and then when i want to create
i can actually ask first for to do list so i want to create a longevity from extension
and the first i will just copy the first answered questions so i have like a five questions
these are five questions and my five answers and i will just pass the answers so we have some
context and now if you prefer the plan for us okay as you can see the first so how should user access
the extension it can be a new tab page replacement quick access or new tab for detailed view
or we have even above so previously you might like many pop-up extensions but i would use
above i would have to have above so that is above and the content source you may hard-core the
base but we can actually add their own content and i want to have it allow users to add today
and content and start locally for now but pre-related content is welcome as well
and now we have a how should you might disappear is a browser notification you have a batch
web pop-up and alerts that will say both the third one it requires notification i will use both
and try to include the pre-related yes
i will use the four and here i will use the third
and i will use both i will see obviously and in the four values please pre-populate
at least of common run derivative reminders all right and i'll just press if you prepare to do this
so we see how it looks as we can see it's planning okay i am i will create beyond so you have
like some of the even project structure versus change and just existing to do this
when i put it in a job dbt we have some design centivics context and reference for now i
don't want any external integration so first i just ask i'm nerding it down and after
pasting the content i'm nerding more down even in to do applications so it automatically
changed to the agent because it has a lot of the information and we see everything here it's pretty
awesome so now we have a lot of details in the mean first thing we have a sleep-up demonstrations
your carrier will sleep hygiene your size nutrition stress management called heat exposure
and for the best view i think it's great to do any other application and see how they handle it
and then eventually extend the functionality so for the first is creating for it creating UI components
background service worker and technical stack and then eventually we can populate and create an agent that
will add new features to our new Chrome extension all right as you can see the extension is already
done it elect 2594 and it's just in a minute once a lot of the extension so obviously to
test it out i will go to management i'll go to Chrome extension to manage extension and i the new one
and because i have a like a longevity i will just press here all right so we cannot see any icons
so in order to fix that obviously i will just open a right tab and see that there is no icons
so i will just move in and find explorer and for now i will just copy it away from the previous one
and we still have some scrapers like metadata tabs that i was creating before but maybe i will
just copy the icons from here it's a very simple maybe i will go to this copy to javity and i will just
pass it here as you can see it has been populated and after it's populated and i will just go and
loud and packed it will unjavity use that folder and then when it's used i will just pop it here
and as you can see you have fun in javity for dashboard we can set our reminders during water posture
check sleep preparation and tablets one it works pretty great and we can open a full dashboard
when you can adjust it you can even set it as a new one so this page was changed but
longevity extension but this way we can obviously equip it by ourselves so i can use keep it
so this time we can exercise and just slip stress management and allow this to pop away it's a
here we can add pop away the new content add some favorite and some reminders it was like very quick
and it's already like very useful and obviously you can just extend from now and create any other
session on top of that.